#### Contact

sbenko@gbmc.org

www.linkedin.com/in/steve-benko-bsn-rn-cen-35779b87 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Emergency Medicine Staffing Services Temporary Staffing

### Certifications

Registered Nurse

CEN

American Cardiovascular Life Support

Pediatric Advanced Life Support

# Steve Benko, BSN, RN, CEN

Nurse Manager- Unit 38 Medicine/Telemetry at GBMC HealthCare Baltimore, Maryland Area

### Summary

Nurse Manager of Unit 38 Medicine/Telemetry. A background of 15 years of experience that includes clinical and leadership positions in Emergency Department and Inpatient settings. Adopting a philosophy that emphasizes patient-centered care and front line staff support. Managing a department with over 10,000 high acuity patient days a year with a wide array of admission diagnoses in a department with 30 inpatient beds. Please visit https://www.gbmc.org/careers if joining this knowledgeable and talented team interests you!

## Experience

GBMC HealthCare 2 years 10 months

Nurse Manager- Medicine/Telemetry March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Towson, Maryland

Interim Manager- Unit 34 January 2020 - Present (7 months) Towson

Clinical Nurse IV October 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 6 months) Towson, Maryland

Interim Emergency Department Manager March 2018 - June 2018 (4 months) Towson, Maryland

Managed a 60,000 visit per year ED with 130 employees

Chesapeake Medical Staffing and Home Care Clinical Liaison, RN September 2011 - October 2017 (6 years 2 months) Lutherville-Timonium, MD RN focused on clinical practice and staff recruitment.

## Education

Stevenson University

Master's degree, Nursing Administration · (2018 - 2020)

University of Maryland Baltimore

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2014)

Carroll Community College

 $\label{eq:Associate} Associate of Arts and Sciences (A.A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered$ 

Nurse · (2004 - 2009)